<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fun on KrolTech</title>
    <link>http://kroltech.com/categories/fun/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fun on KrolTech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 15:56:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://kroltech.com/categories/fun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2013 Year in Review</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2013/12/29/2013-year-in-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 15:56:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2013/12/29/2013-year-in-review/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile app development, Google Dev tools Code School, TekPub</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2013/03/29/mobile-app-development-google-dev-tools-code-school-tekpub/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 19:03:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2013/03/29/mobile-app-development-google-dev-tools-code-school-tekpub/</guid>
      <description>I completed the Code School course on using Google Chrome Dev Tools. I highly recommend you complete this course &amp;#8211; its super quick (probably no longer than 1 hour) and very easy. Yet, I learned a lot. Specifically with the more advanced topics of the dev tools like Profiling, Memory Leaks, Framerates, etc.
Started writing my hybrid mobile app for work &amp;#8211; learned quite a bit along the way. Working with jQuery Mobile, but its overhead and conventions/takeover is making it less than desirable &amp;#8211; perhaps I’ll rewrite the transition animations manually and implement 3rd party Touch/Tap library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript books, recent projects, Line rider!, Rock climbing</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2013/02/08/javascript-books-recent-projects-line-rider-rock-climbing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 18:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2013/02/08/javascript-books-recent-projects-line-rider-rock-climbing/</guid>
      <description>I went on a bit of a shopping spree on Amazon. Besides a few Kindle books (sci-fi, etc) I grabbed a few new JavaScript books as well:
JavaScript Patterns &amp;#8211; Stoyan Stefanov
Secrets of the JavaScript Ninja &amp;#8211; John Resig, Bear Bibeault
If you are looking to utterly destroy an entire afternoon (or more), definitely check out the HTML5 version of an oldie but goodie, Free Rider HD!! (also know as Canvas Rider)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back to work! 1 day Hackathon! Design for developers.</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2013/01/04/back-to-work-hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2013 21:33:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2013/01/04/back-to-work-hackathon/</guid>
      <description>Had a great Christmas/New Years break (well went back to work for 2 days in between there)!! Enjoyed the time off and just spending time with the little one and generally doing nothing productive!
I did find time during the break to spend an entire day working with @Answer7 doing a little mini hackathon! This was something that we have been toying with for a while &amp;#8211; the basic premise is that you and a few friends lock yourself in a room for an entire day and try to create something from scratch!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Most anticipated games of 2013</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/12/10/most-anticipated-games-of-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2012 00:43:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/12/10/most-anticipated-games-of-2013/</guid>
      <description>My list of most anticipated games coming out in 2013 are as follows (most likely in release order):
Anarchy Reigns
DMC &amp;#8211; Devil May Cry, the demo was awesome and haters can all suck it!
Dead Space 3 &amp;#8211; meh, its Dead Space&amp;#8230; 3&amp;#8230;
Aliens: Colonial Marines &amp;#8211; YES!!! I ordered the super deluxe Spec Ed with Power Loader figure!
Metal Gear Rising Revengeance &amp;#8211; YES!!!! The demo for this game was incredible and its from the creators of Bayonetta so need I say more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evil Dead Charlie Brown Remake</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/12/09/evil-dead-charlie-brown-remake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2012 14:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/12/09/evil-dead-charlie-brown-remake/</guid>
      <description>If this ever becomes available as a poster/print I&amp;#8217;m ordering ASAP!

From http://impsandmonsters.blogspot.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Most anticipated movies of 2013</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/12/09/most-anticipated-movies-of-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2012 01:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/12/09/most-anticipated-movies-of-2013/</guid>
      <description>I wrote this post for Fill the Part, but thought I&amp;#8217;d post it here as well for posterity:
(These are in release order.)
Zero Dark Thirty
I&amp;#8217;m a sucker for anything military related, with Black Hawk Down being one of my top 5 movies I can watch over and over. Plus, while I didn&amp;#8217;t absolutely love Hurt Locker, Point Break is another one of my all time favorites.
A Good Day to Die Hard</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacation!!!</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/07/20/vacation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 22:02:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/07/20/vacation/</guid>
      <description>VACATION!! Didn&amp;#8217;t learn much, but did read up some more on XNA programming in general. Rode a wave runner (jet ski) for the first time and that was exhilarating! (Although it was extremely tiring, and very hard work!) Rode lots of rides, ate like shit, and had a great time!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Xbox 360 Kinect review</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2011/01/22/microsoft-xbox-360-kinect-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 16:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2011/01/22/microsoft-xbox-360-kinect-review/</guid>
      <description>First let me get this out of the way to perhaps add some credibility to this review: I am a hardcore gamer and have nearly 30 titles in my Xbox 360 library. I also have a PS3 (although my primary gaming console is the 360). Ive been gaming since I can remember (got a NES for Christmas, had an Atari 2600 etc). With that being said, let me also mention that I have a 4 year old son who is absolutely addicted to Angry Birds on my iPhone, although he&amp;#8217;s not really a fan of using a controller &amp;#8211; just yet.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>