<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Health on KrolTech</title>
    <link>http://kroltech.com/categories/health/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Health on KrolTech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 15:11:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://kroltech.com/categories/health/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tough Mudder Philadelphia 2013</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2013/06/07/tough-mudder-philadelphia-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 15:11:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2013/06/07/tough-mudder-philadelphia-2013/</guid>
      <description>I have successfully finished the Philadelphia Tough Mudder 2013! Not only did I finish, I completed every obstacle! My only problem was the distance / terrain &amp;#8211; it was just way too rough and my knees failed me very early on which lead me to wind up walking more than half the course in incredible pain. But I completed the course!!

I will say, honestly, I don&amp;#8217;t think I ever would want to do it again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barbell club session comes to an end</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2013/03/21/barbell-club-comes-to-an-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 16:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2013/03/21/barbell-club-comes-to-an-end/</guid>
      <description>After 8 long weeks, my cycle with the Barbell Club at Crossfit Generation has come to an end. The entire experience was absolutely incredible, and being that it was my first exposure to true weightlifting I can definitely say without a doubt that I&amp;#8217;m hooked.
In this particular program, the cycle lasts 8 weeks with mandatory 2 days per week. My schedule was Thursday evenings at 6pm and Saturday mornings at 9am, same times every week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript books, recent projects, Line rider!, Rock climbing</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2013/02/08/javascript-books-recent-projects-line-rider-rock-climbing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 18:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2013/02/08/javascript-books-recent-projects-line-rider-rock-climbing/</guid>
      <description>I went on a bit of a shopping spree on Amazon. Besides a few Kindle books (sci-fi, etc) I grabbed a few new JavaScript books as well:
JavaScript Patterns &amp;#8211; Stoyan Stefanov
Secrets of the JavaScript Ninja &amp;#8211; John Resig, Bear Bibeault
If you are looking to utterly destroy an entire afternoon (or more), definitely check out the HTML5 version of an oldie but goodie, Free Rider HD!! (also know as Canvas Rider)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barbell Club, Beard Contests, Tough Mudder!!</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2013/01/10/barbell-club-beard-contests-tough-mudder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 15:10:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2013/01/10/barbell-club-beard-contests-tough-mudder/</guid>
      <description>5am wake up call!! Had to get up at 5 on Monday morning to make sure I was first to register online for the CFG Generation Barbell Club!! Its an 8 week program that focuses on weight training/lifting with an emphasis on technique and improved individual performance. Luckily I got up because by 9:30 all slots were full!
I&amp;#8217;ve been participating in a “Beard Contest” at work, and I can honestly say that I hate it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What easy, sure-fire trick will help you stick to your (new) workout plan?</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2013/01/06/what-easy-sure-fire-trick-will-help-you-stick-to-your-new-workout-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2013 01:34:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2013/01/06/what-easy-sure-fire-trick-will-help-you-stick-to-your-new-workout-plan/</guid>
      <description>If you’re like most people, one of your New Year’s resolutions is to start working out!
However, its no surprise that most local gym memberships skyrocket in January, but attendance is back to regular levels by February.
I&amp;#8217;ve tried working out on and off for years, and its just always been something I&amp;#8217;ve struggled with and never ever succeeded at. I tried the local gym, I tried Xbox Kinect workout “games”, I tried in-home gyms, I tried running using Nike+, I tried just going to the local park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2013 Goals and Ambitions</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/12/21/2013-goals-and-ambitions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2012 20:22:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/12/21/2013-goals-and-ambitions/</guid>
      <description>This is probably going to be one of my last posts for 2012 so I decided to end with a list of my goals and ambitions for the next year! Personally, I think its very important to always have goals and something to look forward to, but also as something to continuously drive yourself to improve. A goal is a destination, and without a destination you&amp;#8217;re just travelling aimlessly with no clear direction or indication of where to go so, ultimately, you wind up nowhere (or right back where you started).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ember.js vs Backbone.js, Responsive Grid Systems, Kinect for Windows, Barbell Club!!</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/12/21/ember-js-vs-backbone-js-responsive-grid-systems-kinect-for-windows-barbell-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2012 15:43:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/12/21/ember-js-vs-backbone-js-responsive-grid-systems-kinect-for-windows-barbell-club/</guid>
      <description>So I spent most of 2 days working through trying to figure out Ember.js. (I know previously I said I was going to focus on Backbone, but I wanted to stick with Ember one more day and try to see it through.) Granted, I’m totally new to this whole MV* side of JavaScript. I had decided that Ember was just the way to go. Sadly, after 2 full days of playing around I&amp;#8217;ve given up (for now) and decided to start focusing on Backbone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protein!, jQuery animation and easing, programming Android, Holiday party!!</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/12/08/protein-jquery-animation-and-easing-programming-android-holiday-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2012 14:53:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/12/08/protein-jquery-animation-and-easing-programming-android-holiday-party/</guid>
      <description>My continued use of My Fitness Pal (nutrition tracking app) has veered dangerously close to obsession! Literally, it&amp;#8217;s become something of a game. I’m constantly looking at the details on every food and considering how it will effect my “stats” (seriously, as if I’m an MMO character or something)! Ultimately, that&amp;#8217;s a good thing I guess. This past weekend alone I&amp;#8217;ve been doing REALLY really well with my eating. I have a great schedule of meals lined up for the week too, with high protein days stacked for Tuesday and Thursday (Crossfit days).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MCSD, Texting from Chrome, Finally changed web hosting providers, Nutrition tracking</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/12/01/mcsd-texting-from-chrome-finally-changed-web-hosting-providers-nutrition-tracking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2012 00:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/12/01/mcsd-texting-from-chrome-finally-changed-web-hosting-providers-nutrition-tracking/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;ve always been interested in some sort of Microsoft certification, and have always had it in the back of my mind to try to complete one of them. This morning I discovered a new track that is perfect and right up my alley; MCSD: Web Applications Developer. Most of the preparation for these exams can be completed via Pluralsight &amp;#8211; so I’m definitely going to try to commit to at least attempting this certification.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>