<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Barbell Club on KrolTech</title>
    <link>http://kroltech.com/tags/barbell-club/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Barbell Club on KrolTech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 16:53:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://kroltech.com/tags/barbell-club/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Barbell club session comes to an end</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2013/03/21/barbell-club-comes-to-an-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 16:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2013/03/21/barbell-club-comes-to-an-end/</guid>
      <description>After 8 long weeks, my cycle with the Barbell Club at Crossfit Generation has come to an end. The entire experience was absolutely incredible, and being that it was my first exposure to true weightlifting I can definitely say without a doubt that I&amp;#8217;m hooked.
In this particular program, the cycle lasts 8 weeks with mandatory 2 days per week. My schedule was Thursday evenings at 6pm and Saturday mornings at 9am, same times every week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First session of the CFG Barbell Club!</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2013/01/18/first-session-of-the-cfg-barbell-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 03:35:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2013/01/18/first-session-of-the-cfg-barbell-club/</guid>
      <description>I had my first session of the Barbell Club tonight and it was absolutely amazing! I hyped it up in my head for so long and then this past week started really getting nervous for it. My biggest fear was that, even though I&amp;#8217;ve been doing Crossfit for 3 months, I haven’t spent any time doing the actual lifts. We covered the basics of the core lifts during on-ramp (my first month), but that was a crash course and 3 months ago!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barbell Club, Beard Contests, Tough Mudder!!</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2013/01/10/barbell-club-beard-contests-tough-mudder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 15:10:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2013/01/10/barbell-club-beard-contests-tough-mudder/</guid>
      <description>5am wake up call!! Had to get up at 5 on Monday morning to make sure I was first to register online for the CFG Generation Barbell Club!! Its an 8 week program that focuses on weight training/lifting with an emphasis on technique and improved individual performance. Luckily I got up because by 9:30 all slots were full!
I&amp;#8217;ve been participating in a “Beard Contest” at work, and I can honestly say that I hate it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>