<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Crossfit on KrolTech</title>
    <link>http://kroltech.com/categories/crossfit/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Crossfit on KrolTech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 15:11:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://kroltech.com/categories/crossfit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tough Mudder Philadelphia 2013</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2013/06/07/tough-mudder-philadelphia-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 15:11:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2013/06/07/tough-mudder-philadelphia-2013/</guid>
      <description>I have successfully finished the Philadelphia Tough Mudder 2013! Not only did I finish, I completed every obstacle! My only problem was the distance / terrain &amp;#8211; it was just way too rough and my knees failed me very early on which lead me to wind up walking more than half the course in incredible pain. But I completed the course!!

I will say, honestly, I don&amp;#8217;t think I ever would want to do it again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barbell club session comes to an end</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2013/03/21/barbell-club-comes-to-an-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 16:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2013/03/21/barbell-club-comes-to-an-end/</guid>
      <description>After 8 long weeks, my cycle with the Barbell Club at Crossfit Generation has come to an end. The entire experience was absolutely incredible, and being that it was my first exposure to true weightlifting I can definitely say without a doubt that I&amp;#8217;m hooked.
In this particular program, the cycle lasts 8 weeks with mandatory 2 days per week. My schedule was Thursday evenings at 6pm and Saturday mornings at 9am, same times every week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week in Review 2/1/13</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2013/02/01/what-i-learned-from-the-single-page-apps-spa-course-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 20:55:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2013/02/01/what-i-learned-from-the-single-page-apps-spa-course-so-far/</guid>
      <description>Was playing with animating some stuff on a page and started trying to work with animating box-shadow. I realized it wasn&amp;#8217;t working and after some research figured out that it just doesn&amp;#8217;t work. A super handy and easy plugin solves that problem though.
The latest episode of the Suburban Strength Coach podcast is up!
Started watching the Single Page Apps with HTML5, Web API, Knockout and jQuery on Pluralsight with my team at work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finishing Last…</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2013/01/30/finishing-last/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2013 16:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2013/01/30/finishing-last/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;ve been doing Crossfit for exactly 4 months now. In that time I have seen and experienced a tremendous improvement in my physical fitness and strength. However, I’m still a noob. And never is it more obvious than at the very end of each workout session. I always, consistently, finish in last place. While there is never a feeling of pressure or intense competition, they do post the scores on the whiteboard, and there are leader-boards and you just can’t help but notice when you finish last!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wodify, Zen Coding, Backbone.js book, SimCity beta!</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2013/01/26/wodify-zen-coding-backbone-js-book-simcity-beta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2013 02:49:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2013/01/26/wodify-zen-coding-backbone-js-book-simcity-beta/</guid>
      <description>Created a super basic/handy lift calculator &amp;#8211; I’ll use this initially during my first bunch of sessions until I get comfortable doing the math on the fly. Its just painful trying to do percentage calculations while lifting, and then breaking down those results into how many different weights you need to add to each side of the bar! This tool will compute all of that in one shot!
My Crossfit box started using Wodify.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First session of the CFG Barbell Club!</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2013/01/18/first-session-of-the-cfg-barbell-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 03:35:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2013/01/18/first-session-of-the-cfg-barbell-club/</guid>
      <description>I had my first session of the Barbell Club tonight and it was absolutely amazing! I hyped it up in my head for so long and then this past week started really getting nervous for it. My biggest fear was that, even though I&amp;#8217;ve been doing Crossfit for 3 months, I haven’t spent any time doing the actual lifts. We covered the basics of the core lifts during on-ramp (my first month), but that was a crash course and 3 months ago!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barbell Club, Beard Contests, Tough Mudder!!</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2013/01/10/barbell-club-beard-contests-tough-mudder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 15:10:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2013/01/10/barbell-club-beard-contests-tough-mudder/</guid>
      <description>5am wake up call!! Had to get up at 5 on Monday morning to make sure I was first to register online for the CFG Generation Barbell Club!! Its an 8 week program that focuses on weight training/lifting with an emphasis on technique and improved individual performance. Luckily I got up because by 9:30 all slots were full!
I&amp;#8217;ve been participating in a “Beard Contest” at work, and I can honestly say that I hate it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What easy, sure-fire trick will help you stick to your (new) workout plan?</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2013/01/06/what-easy-sure-fire-trick-will-help-you-stick-to-your-new-workout-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2013 01:34:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2013/01/06/what-easy-sure-fire-trick-will-help-you-stick-to-your-new-workout-plan/</guid>
      <description>If you’re like most people, one of your New Year’s resolutions is to start working out!
However, its no surprise that most local gym memberships skyrocket in January, but attendance is back to regular levels by February.
I&amp;#8217;ve tried working out on and off for years, and its just always been something I&amp;#8217;ve struggled with and never ever succeeded at. I tried the local gym, I tried Xbox Kinect workout “games”, I tried in-home gyms, I tried running using Nike+, I tried just going to the local park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The ‘Pilgrimage’, Nexus 4 in hand!, Giving Thanks</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/11/23/the-pilgrimage-nexus-4-in-hand-giving-thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2012 22:38:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/11/23/the-pilgrimage-nexus-4-in-hand-giving-thanks/</guid>
      <description>Got the Nexus 4 today and I&amp;#8217;m completely blown away!! Coming from the iPhone4 its literally night and day! I spent probably 4 hours with it tonight just playing around with settings, tinkering with the live wallpapers, and getting my apps installed and all setup. The thing is VERY smooth, and runs like a champ. I&amp;#8217;ve been using it so heavily that I can’t truly speak for the battery yet, as I’ve been killing it and watching it drain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crossfit, Obama!!, Zen Coding</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/11/09/crossfit-obama-zen-coding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 22:35:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/11/09/crossfit-obama-zen-coding/</guid>
      <description>Busted my ass in a major workout last night at Crossfit. The regular class is NO JOKE!
Oh yeah, and Obama won (again)!!!
Decided to try another stab at Angular.js this week. Going to try to lab something up at work using it, something real-world like article comments or something.
Continued working on the new Nextgen.com framework. Got the shell set up pretty nicely and did a lot of organization of all Javascript and CSS and how it will be integrated globally and sitewide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crossfit, Kindle Paperwhite, Philly Code Camp</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/10/05/crossfit-kindle-paperwhite-philly-code-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 22:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/10/05/crossfit-kindle-paperwhite-philly-code-camp/</guid>
      <description>Finally wrapped up the big project at work. Had to have my laptop rebuilt since installing VS2012 broke AD authentication in our app. That made for an interesting debug scenario while we tried to push live and fix bugs!
Started Crossfit! The first class of the on-ramp program really kicked my ass. I thought for sure I was going to throw up by the end, but I hung in there and honestly I think I did pretty well.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>