<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jquery on KrolTech</title>
    <link>http://kroltech.com/tags/jquery/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jquery on KrolTech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2013 13:53:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://kroltech.com/tags/jquery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>ScrollToggle – detect scroll location and trigger events</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2013/06/17/js-library-scrolltoggle-detect-scroll-location-and-trigger-events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2013 13:53:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2013/06/17/js-library-scrolltoggle-detect-scroll-location-and-trigger-events/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passing parameters to click event using trigger</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2013/06/17/quick-tip-passing-parameters-to-click-event-using-trigger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2013 13:44:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2013/06/17/quick-tip-passing-parameters-to-click-event-using-trigger/</guid>
      <description>I have a simple jQuery onClick event bound to a link. On the load of the page, I fetch existing data from a cookie and then call the onClick manually to setup the page (for returning visitors). There is some animation associated with the click &amp;#8211; but when the page loads and all of the clicks are registered, the animations look odd and out of sync (and just logically dont make sense in that situation).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fade in element on event using CSS3  &amp; opacity</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2013/04/15/quick-tip-fade-in-element-on-event-using-css3-opacity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 17:55:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2013/04/15/quick-tip-fade-in-element-on-event-using-css3-opacity/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;m working on a project, that requires a number of different animations based on user events. I recently switched all of the animations to CSS3 transforms and transitions versus jQuery animations. The improvement has been staggering, to say the least.
However, I came across a weird issue today. When attempting to fade an element in after a click event, the element just kept popping into place. It wouldn&amp;#8217;t fade. After some investigation I realized that my jQuery was setting the opacity to 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ImGettin.it launch! DMC!!! JavaScript/Node.js/Backbone.js</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2013/01/18/imgettin-it-launch-dmc-javascriptnode-jsbackbone-js/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 03:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2013/01/18/imgettin-it-launch-dmc-javascriptnode-jsbackbone-js/</guid>
      <description>Soft launched ImGettin.it over the weekend! By soft launch, I mean, bought and setup the domain, and got a test version of the site live. Login works, and the site “works” for the most part, but is very much not ready for prime time yet. I still need to get a lot of things working and most importantly I need a basic admin for the games database. The data that&amp;#8217;s up right now is just test seed data &amp;#8211; while pretty solid is far from complete or even valid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crazy nested for loops (i.e. a Beautiful Mind)</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2013/01/11/crazy-nested-for-loops-i-e-a-beautiful-mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 18:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2013/01/11/crazy-nested-for-loops-i-e-a-beautiful-mind/</guid>
      <description>I was working on a project today, that dealt with a large amount of JSON data. The project needed to allow the user to filter the data by a bunch of different filters and options within those filters.
Initially I started using Underscore.js thinking this would help, but in the interest of time (had to get it done today!!!!) I decided to just do it quick and dirty. Well, I succeeded in the dirty department:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Far Cry 3, NZBMatrix, jqEasing, Functions as parameters?!</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/12/15/far-cry-3-nzbmatrix-jqeasing-functions-as-parameters/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2012 01:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/12/15/far-cry-3-nzbmatrix-jqeasing-functions-as-parameters/</guid>
      <description>Forgot to mention I picked up Far Cry 3 last week and I&amp;#8217;ve been playing it a lot. Its really a fun game. Very open ended, very sandbox. It seems like they finally nailed the balance with the island, the open ended gameplay, gun play, and fun action (I wanted so much to love Far Cry 2 but it just never happened). There are definitely moments where I’m reminded of Skyrim, which is a good thing!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ShiftPanes.js – Shiftable content panes</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/12/12/js-library-shiftpanes-js/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2012 20:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/12/12/js-library-shiftpanes-js/</guid>
      <description>My second JavaScript library in as many days! This new one is called ShiftPanes (like my original names huh?!). Basically, it allows you to declare a container that will hold &amp;#8220;pageable&amp;#8221; blocks of content within it. It is, again, pretty basic and no frills.
Just declare a container with any class you want, and inside declare multiple containers each with the same (different from the container) class that will act as “panes” (or pages).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SlideIns.js – Animate content into a page</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/12/12/jslibrary-slideins-js/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2012 02:59:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/12/12/jslibrary-slideins-js/</guid>
      <description>This is my first ever public JavaScript “library” and also my first GitHub!
SlideIns.js is just simple jQuery code that allows you to have content on a page “slide in” from left, right, or middle (middle just fades in basically). This concept was taken from Apple.com pages, where they recently started having little subtle animations featured on their pages &amp;#8211; for example as you scroll down an iPad or iPhone might slide in from the right of the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wrap your custom JavaScript code in Closure functions</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/12/12/quick-tip-wrap-your-custom-javascript-code-in-closure-functions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2012 02:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/12/12/quick-tip-wrap-your-custom-javascript-code-in-closure-functions/</guid>
      <description>I finally figured out how to use closures properly in JavaScript. This came as a result of my needing to make sure globals I was defining in different script files weren&amp;#8217;t conflicting with same named globals in other files. My solution was rather simple, just wrap existing chunks of code in their own function wrapper:
Original Code:
Note that the variables globalVar and anotherGlobal are truly GLOBAL and any other javascript file(s) with the same variables declared will cause major issues for our code (or vise versa).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>$(document).ready() versus $(window).load()</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/12/11/document-ready-versus-window-load/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 15:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/12/11/document-ready-versus-window-load/</guid>
      <description>As a force of habit, I&amp;#8217;ve always just wrapped my JavaScript code in a $(document).ready() and assumed/hoped for the best. I know that this is specifically for when the DOM is ready, and doesn&amp;#8217;t have anything to do with images. However, 99% of the time I&amp;#8217;ve never really been concerned about the status of loaded images.
Today, I came across an issue where during the $(document).ready() I needed to get the TOP position property of an  element.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protein!, jQuery animation and easing, programming Android, Holiday party!!</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/12/08/protein-jquery-animation-and-easing-programming-android-holiday-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2012 14:53:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/12/08/protein-jquery-animation-and-easing-programming-android-holiday-party/</guid>
      <description>My continued use of My Fitness Pal (nutrition tracking app) has veered dangerously close to obsession! Literally, it&amp;#8217;s become something of a game. I’m constantly looking at the details on every food and considering how it will effect my “stats” (seriously, as if I’m an MMO character or something)! Ultimately, that&amp;#8217;s a good thing I guess. This past weekend alone I&amp;#8217;ve been doing REALLY really well with my eating. I have a great schedule of meals lined up for the week too, with high protein days stacked for Tuesday and Thursday (Crossfit days).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crossfit, Obama!!, Zen Coding</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/11/09/crossfit-obama-zen-coding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 22:35:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/11/09/crossfit-obama-zen-coding/</guid>
      <description>Busted my ass in a major workout last night at Crossfit. The regular class is NO JOKE!
Oh yeah, and Obama won (again)!!!
Decided to try another stab at Angular.js this week. Going to try to lab something up at work using it, something real-world like article comments or something.
Continued working on the new Nextgen.com framework. Got the shell set up pretty nicely and did a lot of organization of all Javascript and CSS and how it will be integrated globally and sitewide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>N-Tier development, iOS development, Doubled internet speeds!</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/10/26/n-tier-development-ios-development-doubled-internet-speeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 22:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/10/26/n-tier-development-ios-development-doubled-internet-speeds/</guid>
      <description>After a discussion about the advantages of N-tier archictecture with a coworker and finally truly understanding it all &amp;#8211; I rewrote the backend for &amp;#8220;Secret&amp;#8221; website to fully utilize a Data, Services, Domain, UI architecture. Now it is coming together quite nicely. I’ve completed the basic groundwork for most of the backend, with the Data layer completed, the Repositories at a good start with most basic CRUD functionality complete, and the Services layer tapping into those repositories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>jQuery; use ON instead of LIVE</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/10/26/quick-tip-jquery-use-on-instead-of-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 02:42:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/10/26/quick-tip-jquery-use-on-instead-of-live/</guid>
      <description>Just learned that jQuery’s .live() should now be replaced with: $(document).on(event,selector, function (e) {});</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Started coding “Secret” website, Azure / hosting pains</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/10/19/started-coding-secret-website-azure-hosting-pains/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2012 22:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/10/19/started-coding-secret-website-azure-hosting-pains/</guid>
      <description>Started coding &amp;#8220;Secret&amp;#8221; website (still not happy with the name)!! Going with a basic 3 tier structure for now &amp;#8211; Domain, Services, and UX. Made good progress so far on the Domain model, and the underlying foundation for the Services layer.
Found and worked with a great tiny little jQuery plugin for working with cookies. Was super easy to use and implemented, and even worked with jQuery 1.3 in a legacy system I needed it in!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use ?? to set value if something is NOT null</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/08/24/quick-tip-use-to-set-value-if-something-is-not-null/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2012 02:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/08/24/quick-tip-use-to-set-value-if-something-is-not-null/</guid>
      <description>Learned to use the ?? operator when checking for null. Use when you want something to = something else only when something else is not null:
var myvar = something_else ?? “default_value”;
myvar will be set to something_else only if something_else is not null, otherwise it will be &amp;#8220;default_value&amp;#8221; instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angular.js, OOP js, Responsive Design, Twitter Bootstrap</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/08/03/angular-js-oop-js-responsive-design-twitter-bootstrap/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2012 22:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/08/03/angular-js-oop-js-responsive-design-twitter-bootstrap/</guid>
      <description>Fresh on the heels of my failure with Knockout, I continued my OOP and data-bound JavaScript development. I also discovered Angular.js this week (by Google). This looks like it&amp;#8217;s a much cleaner and easier (read: less clunky) way of doing what Knockout.js does. It also looks like this might be pretty easy for me to implement into my existing project. Also, from a staying power perspective, it&amp;#8217;s probably safe to assume since Google is officially backing (and created) that it will be around for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knockout.js, jsRender, LESS, SquishIt</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/07/27/knockout-js-jsrender-less-squishit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 22:11:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/07/27/knockout-js-jsrender-less-squishit/</guid>
      <description>This week was all about Knockout.js and my seemingly total lack of understanding of javascript and jquery! After struggling with Knockout (rather, struggling to implement it into an existing project that might be a little too complex for my first attempt with KO) I decided to back burner it for a while. However I did learn a lot more about dealing with data, json, and oop in general with javascript and jquery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XNA 4.0, Kinect, UI Labs</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/07/13/xna-4-0-kinect-ui-labs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 21:59:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/07/13/xna-4-0-kinect-ui-labs/</guid>
      <description>This week and the past have been spent a lot with XNA 4.0 (Xbox Live Indie game development). I did a little bit of work on a project and started looking for good sprite assets for a test game. My idea is to create a DayZ type game but overhead 2D using Zombies Ate My Neighbors! style graphics (in fact the actual sprite sheets from that game itself). Found some great resources for the sprites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog launch, Twitter site integration</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/07/06/july-2-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2012 21:53:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/07/06/july-2-6/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my new blog! This blog is just going to be a weekly/daily journal of sorts, logging all of my discoveries and observations on the Internet and related to development in general. Of course, expect some anecdotes on gaming and life as well!
 Integrated a Twitter feed into the UGM website. Used a tiny bit of jQuery animate to slide the feed bar out from the left side of the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>