<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech on KrolTech</title>
    <link>http://kroltech.com/categories/tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech on KrolTech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 16:42:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://kroltech.com/categories/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why aren’t you using IRC?</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2014/01/22/why-arent-you-using-irc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 16:42:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2014/01/22/why-arent-you-using-irc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You may not realize it, but there&amp;#8217;s a whole world of developers out there accessible in real-time on one of the oldest original &amp;#8220;social networks&amp;#8221;!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connecting Chromecast to a Medialink router</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2013/09/27/connecting-chromecast-to-a-medialink-router/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2013 23:12:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2013/09/27/connecting-chromecast-to-a-medialink-router/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux on my Chromebook, Cloud based IDEs</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2013/05/10/linux-on-my-chromebook-cloud-based-ides/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2013 21:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2013/05/10/linux-on-my-chromebook-cloud-based-ides/</guid>
      <description>Shortly after getting my Chromebook, I quickly realized that it was a bit lacking. Sure, I wrote earlier that its a great little device and perfect for surfing &amp;#8211; but I also sort of wanted something a tiny bit more. So a little bit of searching lead me toan article explaining how you can very easily install Ubuntu Linux (well a port specifically for Chromebooks) on the device! The process itself was super painless and very easy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Asus Chromebook</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2013/04/29/thoughts-on-asus-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 13:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2013/04/29/thoughts-on-asus-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;ve had a bug in my ear lately that I wanted something&amp;#8230; different&amp;#8230; than the iPad for general home usage and Internet surfing etc. I sort of wanted a laptop, but just didn&amp;#8217;t want to pay the money for one. I was looking at some budget ultra-books but even those come in around $800+. There&amp;#8217;s the Surface tablets, but the Pros are also $1200+ and the RT just seems like an iPad basically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MCSD, Texting from Chrome, Finally changed web hosting providers, Nutrition tracking</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/12/01/mcsd-texting-from-chrome-finally-changed-web-hosting-providers-nutrition-tracking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2012 00:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/12/01/mcsd-texting-from-chrome-finally-changed-web-hosting-providers-nutrition-tracking/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;ve always been interested in some sort of Microsoft certification, and have always had it in the back of my mind to try to complete one of them. This morning I discovered a new track that is perfect and right up my alley; MCSD: Web Applications Developer. Most of the preparation for these exams can be completed via Pluralsight &amp;#8211; so I’m definitely going to try to commit to at least attempting this certification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The ‘Pilgrimage’, Nexus 4 in hand!, Giving Thanks</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/11/23/the-pilgrimage-nexus-4-in-hand-giving-thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2012 22:38:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/11/23/the-pilgrimage-nexus-4-in-hand-giving-thanks/</guid>
      <description>Got the Nexus 4 today and I&amp;#8217;m completely blown away!! Coming from the iPhone4 its literally night and day! I spent probably 4 hours with it tonight just playing around with settings, tinkering with the live wallpapers, and getting my apps installed and all setup. The thing is VERY smooth, and runs like a champ. I&amp;#8217;ve been using it so heavily that I can’t truly speak for the battery yet, as I’ve been killing it and watching it drain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Essentials 1.7, Backbone.js, Google Nexus 4, Video game museum gets sold on ebay</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/11/16/web-essentials-1-7-backbone-js-google-nexus-4-video-game-museum-gets-sold-on-ebay/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2012 22:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/11/16/web-essentials-1-7-backbone-js-google-nexus-4-video-game-museum-gets-sold-on-ebay/</guid>
      <description>Installed Web Essentials 1.7 for VS2012 at home and tried out Zen Coding. This is definitely something really awesome and something I wish was integrated a long time ago. As it stands, I don&amp;#8217;t know how much “raw html” I will be coding in the near future to warrant using it all that much &amp;#8211; but I guess any html coding is worth doing via Zen Coding!
Finally spent some time and started doing the Pluralsight course on Backbone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Sandy, Windows 8, NFS: Most Wanted</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/11/02/hurricane-sandy-windows-8-nfs-most-wanted/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2012 22:34:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/11/02/hurricane-sandy-windows-8-nfs-most-wanted/</guid>
      <description>Hurricane Sandy!!!
Installed Windows 8 over the weekend. At first, it was a little jarring. The changes are sweeping. Im not sure how I feel still about basically the start menu being expanded to an entire screen &amp;#8211; which is basically what happened. The live tiles concept is neat. I&amp;#8217;m not really a fan of forcing “metro” style apps to run full screen &amp;#8211; as I have a fairly large screen and typically development environments are the only programs I ever run maximized.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>N-Tier development, iOS development, Doubled internet speeds!</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/10/26/n-tier-development-ios-development-doubled-internet-speeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 22:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/10/26/n-tier-development-ios-development-doubled-internet-speeds/</guid>
      <description>After a discussion about the advantages of N-tier archictecture with a coworker and finally truly understanding it all &amp;#8211; I rewrote the backend for &amp;#8220;Secret&amp;#8221; website to fully utilize a Data, Services, Domain, UI architecture. Now it is coming together quite nicely. I’ve completed the basic groundwork for most of the backend, with the Data layer completed, the Repositories at a good start with most basic CRUD functionality complete, and the Services layer tapping into those repositories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crossfit, Kindle Paperwhite, Philly Code Camp</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/10/05/crossfit-kindle-paperwhite-philly-code-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 22:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/10/05/crossfit-kindle-paperwhite-philly-code-camp/</guid>
      <description>Finally wrapped up the big project at work. Had to have my laptop rebuilt since installing VS2012 broke AD authentication in our app. That made for an interesting debug scenario while we tried to push live and fix bugs!
Started Crossfit! The first class of the on-ramp program really kicked my ass. I thought for sure I was going to throw up by the end, but I hung in there and honestly I think I did pretty well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Philly Tech Meetup, Autocomplete</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/09/14/first-philly-tech-meetup-autocomplete/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 22:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/09/14/first-philly-tech-meetup-autocomplete/</guid>
      <description>Attended a Philly Tech Meetup in Center City (Market Street &amp;#8211; Science Center). Was very informative, and definitely will not be the last!
Learned about autocomplete=”off” as an HTML attribute. Was having an issue with validation where the browser was prepopulating the New Password field in the form with what was saved for the users login credentials. This was throwing the error because New Password (auto completed) didnt match the corresponding Confirm Password (which was naturally blank).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MVC postback bug, Underscore.js, ===, Asana, Launched FillThePart.com!!, Visual Studio 2012</title>
      <link>http://kroltech.com/2012/09/07/mvc-postback-bug-underscore-js-asana-launched-fillthepart-come-visual-studio-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2012 22:20:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jkat98@gmail.com (Jason Krol)</author>
      <guid>http://kroltech.com/2012/09/07/mvc-postback-bug-underscore-js-asana-launched-fillthepart-come-visual-studio-2012/</guid>
      <description>After being stumped for a while with a particularly interesting issue in MVC &amp;#8211; I found the solution on Rick Strahl’s blog. Specifically I was trying to change the values of a view model from a controller action, after PostBack &amp;#8211; yet my changes seemed to be ignored or simply refuse to stick. Turns out the HtmlHelpers refer to the actual POST data on page load after postback (seemingly ignoring the “model” even though you explicitly refer to the model when using HtmlHelpers).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>